Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary?
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache.
And through the pain.
Know that I will be there.
To stand by you.
Like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard!
And bring along all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on the crew.
We are.
You just never learn, do you? Let's go!
I'll pay you later!
Any way you want.
You made a boy cry?
He made me mad.
Oh, it's okay.
Kids won't be kids.
He said your tangerine
sucks. He what? Bellamere!
Never give up.
You must find the strength
inside you to always move on.
You must live through every moment.
And if you can smile in the face of
it all that is the greatest dream
while I'm in charge those without money
will die now do you understand me you worms
what's this?
That's my map!
I drew it and you can't have it!
A child drew this?
Give it back! No!
Huh.
Very good.
She could be useful.
Bring her with us. Right?
No!
Why did I go?
Why did I go to trouble?
You promised not to hurt
her if you got your money.
Right.
I won't hurt you.
Just borrow her for a while.
Genzo, help me!
I won't let you take her! Karumi.
Genzo!
Genzo, get her!
I'll save you, Nami.
I won't let you go.
No, please!
It's okay, you don't need to save me!
Enough of this!
I will save you!
Please, no more killing!
All of our ships have been sunk.
I'm afraid our plan to have Nami and
Nojiko escape to the sea was a bad plan.
The Marines won't bother
trying to save us.
We've lost our island.
Bellamere knew that this would happen.
Her experiences in the Marines taught her
what all these creatures are capable of.
She knew that none of us would escape.
They've taken Nami!
What am I supposed to do now?
Bellamy!
We know where Arlong and his crew are.
It looks like they're going to
settle right here on this island.
It's time to decide.
We can fight to the death right now,
or we can take a chance that the
Marines will someday come to save us?
and hope and pray we don't
get killed before then.
Your choice!
Only Marine Headquarters
stands a chance against them.
But they have their hands
full with the Grand Line.
The chances that they would come all the
way out here for us are as good as zero.
But I can't just sit
here and abandon Nami.
We must fight!
I'm in.
I can't just stand by and do
nothing when a child is in danger.
Now who else will come fight beside us?
I don't care.
Do you kill me?
I'm going to save that little brat.
Tell him your favorite life.
You can't quit now.
We should do no less.
Let's fight!
It's just one of us fights,
they'll blame us all.
So let's do it!
Nami! Nami!
Nami! What? You're okay!
Everyone look!
Are you okay?
Did they hurt you any?
Hey!
I'm joining you.
Huh?
I'm joining Arlong's crew!
I'll get to be a navigator and draw maps.
What in the world are you talking about?
Stand back Did they threaten to
do something terrible to you?
Please, tell me. No.
They must have done something.
No, no.
Tell the truth.
Let go of me. Nami?
But that's an Arlong tattoo, not you. Why?
Look at this.
They gave me all this money.
They say, don't buy me
anything I want. No!
I will never forgive you if you join them.
Don't you understand?
They killed Bellemere in front of us!
She died to keep us safe!
I'll never forgive you! Never!
You're not my sister!
Who cares?
Why would I want to live like
Bellemere if it just gets you killed?
I don't want to die like that!
How could you?
Bellemere?
Bellemere gave her life so that you
and I could go on living together!
That's enough, Nojiko.
Leave us, Nami!
Never set foot in this village again.
Help me!
I don't understand.
How could she betray her family like that?
For money?
Bellamy was like her mother.
Nami loved Bellamere.
I know she did.
Hey, didn't Bellamere always say?
Good things will come your way!
as long as you continue to live?
Lots of good things.
Yes.
After Arlong took me, I watched him sink
five marine ships like they were toys.
I don't think they'll send anymore.
We're on our own.
So I decided I'd do something about it.
I made a deal with Arlong to
buy Cocoyashi Village from...
Buy Cocoyashi? How?
For a hundred million berries.
If I buy the town, we'll be free.
No one else will die.
And all I have to do is
join his crew and draw maps.
But a hundred million berries?
You can't earn that
working your whole life!
I will get that money no matter what!
People are having a hard enough
time paying their own tribute.
So I have to do this alone.
If anyone tries to help
me, they'll just get hurt.
Won't it be hard?
Yeah, living with the people
who killed our mother.
I'll be okay.
I'll just smile every time I see his face.
I'm not gonna cry anymore.
I'm gonna fight by myself.
To make a choice like that
when you're only ten years old?
Do you know how hard that must have been?
All to save the village she loves so much.
That girl...
Whoever makes Nami suffer
is going to hear from me!
Oh, why'd you do that?
Because I'm telling you to stay out of it.
If you go around saying
that she's your friend,
they're going to become suspicious of her.
Then her eight years of suffering
will have been for nothing.
Don't make it harder than it already is.
She has to fight alone.
Knowing there are people who call her
friend only makes the suffering worse.
A pirate thief that's right
the only thing this place
has going for it is plenty
of pirates to steal from
i'm gonna make them pay
you're all cut up yeah i kind
of screwed up but look one
million Who cares about that?
You need a doctor!
It's nothing.
These cups are nothing.
No one will find it here.
I'll save up, little by little.
By the time this is filled,
I'll have my hundred million.
Still a long way to go.
One hundred million berries.
It's taken a while, but
only seven million left.
I can get that with one more job.
Just one more trip!
And this will finally be over.
Arlong's rule will be over.
Cocoyashi Village will be free.
I will be free.
And then?
And then I think I'll finally be
able to smile again. For real!
Bellamere.
So why do the marines want Nami?
Your job is to lead the way quietly.
A hat pinwheel.
Where in the world did he get that?
It's so cool!
One more little job.
Well, let's get to it.
Enies?
And the Marines?
Are you the pirate thief known as Name?
The marine sources have
revealed that you have quite a
large sum of treasure that
you've stolen from pirates.
The government hereby confiscates
everything you've stolen.
It is required that
you comply immediately.
Do you understand?
I'm only going to warn you once.
I'm one of the leaders
of the Arlong Pirates.
If you mess with me, Arlong
won't sit by quietly.
Silly girl.
Who do you think I am?
Do you honestly think
you can intimidate me?
Find the stolen goods!
Don't move!
I said stop!
Do you really think this is what
the Marines should be doing now?
The Arlong pirates are murderers.
They've destroyed entire cities
and you're doing nothing!
He's ruling over this island and
trampling over people's lives.
You'd ignore Arlong's atrocities
to steal from a thief?
Is that what you stand for?
Big talk from a filthy criminal.
Continue the search, man.
Every person on this
island has been waiting
for the Marines to come
and help them for years.
How dare you pass them by and
come here searching for money?
Colonel, this tangerine orchard
seems a little suspicious.
Dig it up.
The whole thing, if need be.
Keep your filthy hands off
Bellamere's Tangerine Orchard!
I won't let you take my money!
That money's for...
it's for...
That poor girl's money is meant
to save Pokayashi Village.
What gives you the right to take our
salvation away from her? Damn you!
My, my.
A mere village representative
talking down to a marine colonel.
How bold.
Genzo, how'd you know about that?
I've always known, Nami.
I couldn't believe what you had done.
So I confronted Nojiko about it later.
Since then,
everyone has known that
you stayed with the
Arlong pirates so that you
could save the village.
But we all agreed we'd
never tell you that we knew.
If you ever thought the villagers
were placing their hopes on you,
you might never leave his gang
for fear of letting us down?
That can't be!
Now hold on a minute, just what
are you trying to say here?
Are you telling me that the villagers are
thieves and we should
arrest every one of them?
Is that what you're saying?
What he's saying is that every last
one of us is fighting to survive.
We have to fend for
ourselves because we can't
rely on support from
you government people!
So, if you're not going to protect our
village, then get the hell out of here.
And be quick about it, or
Arlong will sink your ship, too.
Arlong will.
I wouldn't be so sure.
You still haven't found it?
We're looking for a hundred million
berries here, not a grain of rice!
Hey, you!
How do you know how much there is?
Oh, I don't know.
I just have a hunch that that's
the amount we're looking for.
It's him.
Tell me!
It was Erlong that sent you, wasn't it?
Of course not.
I wouldn't do a pirate's dirty work.
That'd be wrong.
I'm just a public servant dealing with
theft the way any government worker would.
You corrupt marine scumbag!
The marine comes due to being
nothing but pirate cronies!
Arlong!
Sir, I found it!
Incredible.
I must say I'm impressed you've
gathered this much treasure.
The money's all ragged and
bloody. No matter. Money's money.
30 % of this is all mine.
Don't touch that.
Don't touch that. Nami!
Stop it!
Don't touch that!
No! No! No!
No! No!
No!
Nojiko!
Doctor! Doctor!
Genzo, what is it?
Nojiko's been shot. By who?
The Marines. The Marines?
Nami?
Hey, Nami!
What's up?
Need help with anything?
Why are you still here?
Stay out of my business!
Just get away from our island!
Arlong!
I bet it's the village.
You want it left alone.
Arlong!
Gather up 100 million
berries, then bring it to me.
Do so and I will let your village go,
in addition to giving you your freedom.
Arlong!
And I'm the kind of fish
man who would rather
die than break an
agreement concerning money.
And I don't even care
how long it takes you.
I will honor our agreement.
Arlong!
What's her problem?
Hmm? Hmm?
Ah, what seems to be the problem,
oh skilled surveyor of ours?
Why the sour face?
Those marine maggots you keep on the
payroll stole every last berry I had.
What happened to all that crap about
dying before you'd ever break a promise?
when it comes to money, bastard?
Refresh my memory.
Did I break a promise?
Don't play dumb with me!
I know that you've teamed
up with the Marines!
Just when did I break that promise?
Speak up, girl.
Damn.
Damn you. Damn you!
Too bad.
All your stolen money got stolen.
That certainly is unfortunate.
But a deal is a deal, Nami.
If you can't come up
with 100 million berries,
then both you and your village
stay in my possession indefinitely.
Well, you know the terms.
You pig!
It's only 100 million berries.
Start saving again and
you'll have it in no time.
Or are you gonna run out on me?
Listen, if you do that, I'll kill everyone
in that village Do you understand me?
Nami, we agreed we would
never tell you that we knew.
If you thought all of
us were counting on you?
You would be bound by guilt never to leave
his gang for fear of letting us down.
Ah, running away so soon!
Shouldn't we chase after her?
No need for that.
Trust me, Hachi.
She's not going anywhere.
There's no way Nami could just abandon
the lives of all those villagers.
Now that's what I call playing dirty.
There's no way I'd let go of
an asset like Nami that easily.
I may be cruel, but I'm
not totally heartless.
Once she's done charting all the
world's oceans, she'll have her freedom.
That's pretty harsh, man.
It'll take decades for sure.
Yeah, it's been a hundred
years, wouldn't it be enough?
We've had enough. Take up arms.
It's time to fight!
Genzo, please don't do anything stupid!
We have to live or our
struggles will mean nothing!
You can't throw your lives away!
Eight long years ago, we promised
we wouldn't live our lives in vain.
No matter the pain or humiliation
we endured under Arlong,
We swore to fight the long fight
so Nami could meet their demands.
But they lied.
They never intended to
keep their end of the deal.
Instead, they stole our
only chance at freedom.
So now,
we should make those
filthy fishmen pay for
the years they manipulated
that kind young girl.
Am I right?
Yeah, let's do this.
We were always ready to
fight those monsters.
Let's get them.
Time to show those lousy, stinking
fishmen what we're made of.
Yeah!
Everybody, wait!
Huh?
Nami.
Calm down.
It's not that much money.
I can make it back in no time.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
It'll be easy this time.
I'm used to it.
I'll be fine. Just relax.
Everything is okay.
Hey, it's nothing compared to back then.
It's okay.
You don't need to save me.
Come on, everyone.
I'm perfectly fine.
You've done enough.
You have to know that
there is no point now.
You struggled so hard carrying our
lives on your back this whole time.
I can only imagine that
joining them must have been
more painful than being
stabbed through the heart.
You fought very well.
Genzo?
Set yourself free from this village
Nami, do it! What? Nojiko!
Nami... Go on.
You're an exceptional young woman!
And you have a dream?
Everyone, listen!
I won't let you go!
Just stay right there!
I'm not going to let anyone
else get hurt by these monsters!
You'll all die.
We know that.
Nami, it's no use.
We've made up our minds.
Get out of the way!
Move out!
We may not win, but we
will give them hell!
Ha-ha-ha.
Arlug!
Luffy
What do you want?
You don't know anything about this.
You don't know what's been happening on
this island for the past eight years.
Nope, I don't.
This has nothing to do with you.
I told you to leave this place.
Yep, you sure did.
So leave.
I told you to leave!
Get out of here!
Get out of here now!
Go!
Go away! Go! Go! Go!
Luffy...
Help me...
Of course.
That's what friends do.
He's gonna pay!
You better keep your hands off my hat!
Luffy?
Let's go.
Right.
Hey, are you guys all right?
Did Arlong do this to you?
Move aside.
We have business to take
care of with the fishmen.
When we finally found out the
truth about Big Sist Nami,
we realized the only thing we could
do was defeat Arlong in battle.
So we decided to come back
here and challenge him.
Yeah, then we lost, but only by a hair.
I'm sorry, but I can't
let you through this door.
You have no chance of victory!
What's that?
Be patient.
It won't be long now!
You see, we're waiting for
the arrival of certain men.
What certain men?
Don't worry.
They'll be here soon!
I'd bet my life on it.?
There!
It's them.
Why would they come to defend our village?
If those men can't handle Arlong and
his gang, then there really is no hope.
Not only for this island,
but for the whole East Blue.
Those are the faces of the four men
who are here to change your destiny.
Earn their images into your memory.
Step aside! Ah!
Hey,
do you think those two idiots that showed
up earlier are members of
Zoro's little crew? Zoro?
They seem too weak for that.
They weren't even worth killing.
That's for sure!
What the...
Now, which one of you is Arlong?
As I watched the sunrise,
I began to wonder.
What could be the reason
it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you.
Show me how to catch those
feelings, get on to come back to me!
I'll do what I must be.
Cause they're everything I want to be.
Pass these arms around my dreams.
And pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way.